{"posts":[{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi were there answers for tute 7 part 2 written 1. consider the following user-stories and implement a set of test-cases to match the acceptance criteria thanks.","answers":[{"text":"hi the answers should be available now in the tut/lab 7 section","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi will we have questions that really need to be run in python i mean i know we will be asked on writing some code like pytest class. will these code be run or just look","answers":[{"text":"yes","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"so we have to use python during exam do we need to install pytest in the exam","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"it s pre-installed.","theta":1,"count":0}]]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"where is information on the purpose of strategy design pattern","answers":[{"text":"you are expected to know only about the uml of a strategy design pattern and generally what it does. the actual fine details is taught in 2511. for your interest strategy pattern enables selection of algorithms at run time. essentially what happens is there is a behaviour or algorithm class which abstracts multiple types of algorithms ie. sort abstracts quicksort bubblesort yet all the types of sorts are in their own class and implement sort function differently. run-time means that during execution of code we can essentially inject this sorting behaviour by instantiating a sort object one that extends sort class and placing it inside any object which is able to utilise its sorting behaviours. we can treat sorts all the same way because of abstraction sortingalgorithm.sort for example.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"how do we run pytest on cse machines i have installed pytest but when i run pytest -v xxx it says pytest command not found. thank you.","answers":[{"text":"use the virtual environment or try python3 -m pytest.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"composition vs ocp. for the car wash class diagram in the practice test it claims the class job is a composition of class joblist. this means an instance of job should only be instantiated inside the joblist function add_job. however if we were to conform to ocp the job instance should be instantiated outisde this function so we do not need to change the arguments passed into add_job unlike the composition example . i just want some clarification on this and which one would be more correct.","answers":[{"text":"ocp relates to extending behaviour without modifying source code. i would argue that add_job does the exact same thing you are not extending behaviour you are simply adding one more argument to allow it to do what it was intended to do. this could be more of an issue of fragility . i would say that both approaches are perfectly reasonable it would depend if you wanted to enforce composition or not. if you are pedantic enough one could create a parameter class for storing job information to be passed in. this itself could turn into an issue.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi will both unittests and pytest be assessed or just pytest thanks.","answers":[{"text":"only pytest. unittest will not be examined","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi in examined lecture content it says this week 05 - no html 5/css flask python decorators does this mean all these things won't be examined since all other parts are the content which will be examined i'm a bit confused about this line.","answers":[{"text":"you will not be writing html css or flask in the exam.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"is www and web architecture in the exam","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"no you will not be questioned on www http request/response etc.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"so is any of week 5 examinable","theta":1,"count":0}]]]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"for quiz 3 the marks in my grades show that i'm still missing a mark due to the adjustment with question 4 i've double checked with the given answers has this been changed in the database and just isn't shown in my grades","answers":[{"text":"yes this will not be reflected on webcms3 it will be internally adjusted on our database as we process the final marks","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"will we have to do any coding in flask for the exam","answers":[{"text":"no please follow the revision guide which under your lecture 13 lecture content.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"can we see the answer to tutorial week10","answers":[{"text":"it is visible now.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"can we please have the answers to quiz 3","answers":[{"text":"it's under week 13' contents of your lectures.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"when will we know quiz 3 marks","answers":[{"text":"hi it should be up by now","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"how to check which of these i was right and wrong thanks","theta":1,"count":0}]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"so there are no week13 tutes/labs my timetable shows otherwise..","answers":[{"text":"no week 13 tuts/labs as tuts amp labs commenced in week 1 this semester.","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi are methods of an object meant to be functions on themselves only or can an object student for example have a method called searchclasses whereby it interacts with object called classesmanager which contains a list of classes. student.searchclasses would perform a search through the list of classes in classesmanager. is this thought process and understanding of methods correct sorry that was a bit much to understand but to try to condense are object methods meant to be independent of other objects so they can exists independently and all their methods work without the existence of other objects thank you","answers":[{"text":"edit to answer your question about method independence when an object is instantiated myobj object this specific instance of the object is unique and differentiated from any other instance you may create. note that the majority of methods defined basically all in this course in the class require an object instance of the class to exist to even use them. they can be referred to instance methods. i can use them calling myobj.method","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"that makes sense thank you","theta":1,"count":0}],{"text":"methods are typically responsible for attributes of itself or possibly of objects of which it aggregates or composes. from what you are saying wouldn't it make more sense for the classesmanager to have the method which searches through the classes list it holds don't think physically in terms of a student doing it.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"sorry for bothering from what you are saying if students want to see the information of classes this viewing method is better to put under classmanager rather than student right because the classmanager actually holds the information.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"if a student wishes to view all available classes this information is simply pulled from classmanager through a classmanager method like getclasses then displayed via a for-loop which can be done easily on html. if a student wanted to search there simply would be a search method in classmanager to return a list of the relevant classes to display. not always are object methods simply acting upon themselves although they are utilising some data they are already holding at the very least.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"get it thank you very much","theta":1,"count":0}]]],[{"text":"would you say it's correct to think of methods as 'things done on the object rather than by the object'","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"that wouldn't be a bad way to think about it. although i wouldn't be overly stringent on sticking to mantras or design principles. they are mostly to give you a general idea of good design.","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"ok thank you","theta":1,"count":0}]]]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"hi i just found the quiz can be submitted more than once is this designed to be so or it is only me having an unstable internet connection.","answers":[{"text":"not sure if intended but other students have stated they have been able to. edit should only be for this week","theta":1,"count":0}]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"are we required to program using a certain version of python if so what version thanks","answers":[{"text":"python3 latest version","theta":1,"count":0},[{"text":"thank you","theta":1,"count":0}]]},{"intent":"assignments","courseCode":"COMP1531","tags":[{"name":"forums","salience":0.5,"theta":1},{"name":"comp1531 front page","salience":0.5,"theta":1}],"question":"for the setup task i already have an account on github and it is a student account so it allows for free private repos. i'm just wondering whether an education account is the same thing as a student account or if an education account includes the pack https //education.github.com/students","answers":[{"text":"hi alex as long as you can use private repos for free it's all good that is all we need it for - no need to apply for the education pack again. hope this helped cheers ian","theta":1,"count":0}]}]}